[
  {
    "question": "An interaction model is a dynamic model that shows how the system interacts with its environment as it\n            is used.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "An interaction application is a dynamic model that not shows how the system interacts with its environment as\n          it is used.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The weather forecast system is not establishing a satellite communication link with the weather station and\n          requests transmission of the data.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The weather station sends a summary of the weather data that has been collected from the instruments in\n            the collection period to the weather information system",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The weather station is composed of independent subsystems that not communicate by\n            broadcasting messages on a system architecture.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Application domain objects that are ‘_____’ objects related to the instruments in the system.",
    "choices": [
      "Hardware",
      "Object",
      "System",
      "Software"
    ],
    "answer": "Hardware"
  },
  {
    "question": "Encapsulates the summarized data from the instruments.",
    "choices": [
      "Forecast Data",
      "System Data",
      "Weather Data",
      "Application Data"
    ],
    "answer": "Weather Data"
  },
  {
    "question": "_______ show the objects and object classes and relationships between these entities.",
    "choices": [
      "Sample Model",
      "Design Model",
      "Grand Model",
      "Class Model"
    ],
    "answer": "Design Model"
  },
  {
    "question": "_______ describe the dynamic interactions between objects.",
    "choices": [
      "Design Model",
      "Dynamic Model",
      "System Model",
      "Class Model"
    ],
    "answer": "Dynamic Model"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is the most modern software is constructed by reusing existing components or systems.",
    "choices": [
      "Configuration Management",
      "Host-Target Development",
      "Reuse",
      "Management Development"
    ],
    "answer": "Reuse"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is where you call the object or method to be tested.",
    "choices": [
      "Assertion Part",
      "Call Part",
      "Setup Part"
    ],
    "answer": "Call Part"
  },
  {
    "question": "This means that there should be at least one test for every requirement in the requirements\n            document.",
    "choices": [
      "Program Testing",
      "Test Software",
      "Custom software"
    ],
    "answer": "Custom software"
  },
  {
    "question": "Guideline-based testing, where you use testing guidelines to choose test cases.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Test software with sequences which have two value.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Force computation results to be too large or too small.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "TDD was not introduced as part of agile methods such as Extreme Programming.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Every code segment that you write has at least two associated test so all code written has\n            at least one test.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The level of confidence depends on how critical the software is to an organisation.",
    "choices": [
      "Marketing environment",
      "Software purpose",
      "User expectations"
    ],
    "answer": "Software purpose"
  },
  {
    "question": "Users may have low expectations of certain kinds of software.",
    "choices": [
      "User expectations",
      "Software purpose",
      "Marketing environment"
    ],
    "answer": "User expectations"
  },
  {
    "question": "Concerned with analysis of the static system representation to discover problems  (static verification)",
    "choices": [
      "Software Testing",
      "User expectations",
      "Software Inspections"
    ],
    "answer": "Software Inspections"
  },
  {
    "question": "System configure model is a not structural model that demonstrates the other subsystems in the environment of\n          the system being developed.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The weather station is composed of independent subsystems that communicate by broadcasting messages on a\n            common infrastructure",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Object identification is an iterative process. You are unlikely to get it right first time.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "A _____ is a package of software controlled instruments which collects data,\n            performs some data processing and transmits this data for further processing.",
    "choices": [
      "Weather Station",
      "Forecast Station",
      "Object Station",
      "Class Station"
    ],
    "answer": "Weather Station"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of pattern elements is the results and trade-offs of applying the pattern.",
    "choices": [
      "Consequences",
      "Problem Description",
      "Solution Description",
      "Name"
    ],
    "answer": "Consequences"
  },
  {
    "question": "At this level, you directly reuse objects from a library rather than writing the code yourself.",
    "choices": [
      "The object level",
      "The system level",
      "The component level",
      "The abstraction level"
    ],
    "answer": "The object level"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ is the name given to the general process of managing a changing software system.",
    "choices": [
      "Management Development",
      "Host-Target Development",
      "Configuration Management",
      "Reuse"
    ],
    "answer": "Configuration Management"
  },
  {
    "question": "The most software is developed on one computer (the host), but runs on a separate machine (the target).",
    "choices": [
      "Reuse",
      "Configuration Management",
      "Host-Target Development",
      "Management Development"
    ],
    "answer": "Host-Target Development"
  },
  {
    "question": "Structured object-oriented design processes involve developing a number of different system models.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Program Testing?",
    "choices": [
      "intended to show that a program does what it is intended to do and to discover program defects before\n                  it is put into use.",
      "defect testing can be deliberately obscure and need not reflect how the system is normally used.",
      "the system to perform correctly using a given set of test cases that reflect the system’s expected\n                  use."
    ],
    "answer": "intended to show that a program does what it is intended to do and to discover program defects before\n                  it is put into use."
  },
  {
    "question": "Concerned with exercising and observing product behaviour (dynamic verification)",
    "choices": [
      "User expectations",
      "Software Inspections",
      "Software Testing"
    ],
    "answer": "Software Testing"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is where a separate testing team test a complete version of the system before it is\n            released to users.",
    "choices": [
      "Release Testing",
      "Development testing",
      "User Testing"
    ],
    "answer": "Release Testing"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is where some or all of the components in a system are integrated and the system is\n            tested as a whole.",
    "choices": [
      "Component Testing",
      "Unit testing",
      "System Testing"
    ],
    "answer": "System Testing"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is where you initialize the system with the test case, namely the inputs and expected\n            outputs.",
    "choices": [
      "Call Part",
      "Setup Part",
      "Assertion Part"
    ],
    "answer": "Setup Part"
  },
  {
    "question": "Input data and output results often fall into different classes where all members of a\n            class are related.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Force invalid inputs to be generated",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Parameter interfaces Data passed from two method or procedure to another.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "User testing is essential, even when comprehensive system and release testing have been\n            carried out.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Getting a product to market early may be more important than finding defects in the\n            program.",
    "choices": [
      "User expectations",
      "Marketing environment",
      "Software purpose"
    ],
    "answer": "Marketing environment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Software design and implementation activities are invariably outerwear-leaved.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Object identification is an looping process. You are unlikely to get it right second time.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Use a scenario based approach and identify objects based on what participates in what behaviour.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "This is the basic interface of the weather station to its environment.",
    "choices": [
      "Weather Station",
      "Subsystem Station",
      "Forecast Station",
      "System Station"
    ],
    "answer": "Weather Station"
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ are used to show how objects respond to different service requests and the state transitions\n            triggered by these requests.",
    "choices": [
      "File Diagram",
      "State Diagram",
      "System Diagram",
      "Subsystem Diagram"
    ],
    "answer": "State Diagram"
  },
  {
    "question": "At this level, you don’t reuse software directly but use knowledge of successful abstractions in the\n            design of your software.",
    "choices": [
      "The abstraction level",
      "The system level",
      "The object level",
      "The component level"
    ],
    "answer": "The abstraction level"
  },
  {
    "question": "At this level, you reuse entire application systems.",
    "choices": [
      "The abstraction level",
      "The system level",
      "The object level",
      "The component level"
    ],
    "answer": "The system level"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is where individual program units or object classes are tested.",
    "choices": [
      "System Testing",
      "Component Testing",
      "Unit testing"
    ],
    "answer": "Unit testing"
  },
  {
    "question": "The test expect the system to perform correctly using a given set of test cases that reflect the\n              system’s expected use.",
    "choices": [
      "Validating Testing",
      "Defect testing",
      "Custom testing"
    ],
    "answer": "Validating Testing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Every code segment that you write has at least one associated test so all code written has at least one\n            test.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The test cases in defect testing can be deliberately obscure and need not reflect how the\n            system is normally used.",
    "choices": [
      "Custom Testing",
      "Validating Testing",
      "Defect Testing"
    ],
    "answer": "Defect Testing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Software design and implementation activities are invariably inter-leaved.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The weather substation sends a summary of the system data that has been not collected\n            from the instruments in the collection period to the weather information system.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "It Provides a standard way of accessing the elements in a collection, irrespective of how that\n            collection is implemented (Iterator pattern).",
    "choices": [
      "Design Problems",
      "Class Problems",
      "System Problems",
      "Object Problems"
    ],
    "answer": "Design Problems"
  },
  {
    "question": "They require a lot of effort for development and maintenance of these models and, for small systems,\n            this may not be cost-effective.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is where the system is tested during development to discover bugs and defects.",
    "choices": [
      "Development testing",
      "User Testing",
      "Release Testing"
    ],
    "answer": "Development testing"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is where you identify groups of inputs that have common characteristics and should be\n              processed in the same way.",
    "choices": [
      "Unit testing",
      "Partition Testing",
      "System Testing"
    ],
    "answer": "Partition Testing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Input data and output results often fall into similar classes where all members of a class\n            are related.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "It concern with rooting out undesirable system behavior such as system crashes, unwanted interactions\n            with other systems, incorrect computations and data corruption.",
    "choices": [
      "Defect testing",
      "Test software",
      "Custom software"
    ],
    "answer": "Defect testing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Regression test suite is not developed incrementally as a program is developed.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  }
]